[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Check it out, Anne. The cafe may be empty,
- 看看这个，Anne。咖啡馆可能是空的，
but the rest of the store is still bringing them in.
但商店的其他部分还在吸引顾客。
- Well, except that line is headed out.
- 嗯，除了那条队伍正在往外延伸。
[gasps] And so are Dawn and Mae.
[吸气声] Dawn和Mae也是。
This isn't good.
这不太妙。
Dawn, what are you guys doing?
Dawn，你们在做什么？
- We're in line Captain Felde's cafe down the street.
- 我们在街那头的Felde上尉咖啡馆排队。
- [gasps] You're cheating on our cafe?
- [吸气声] 你们在背叛我们的咖啡馆吗？
- Do your brothers know?
- 你哥哥们知道吗？
all: Oh, we know.
all: 哦，我们知道。
- [gasps] - All of you?
- [惊讶] - 你们都知道？
[gasps] And all your friends?
[惊讶] 还有你所有的朋友？
After all the free smoothies I gave you kids.
毕竟我给你们这些孩子免费送了那么多冰沙。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. You give them free smoothies?
- 哇，哇，哇。你给他们免费冰沙？
- I just want them to like me, Anne.
- 我只是想让他们喜欢我，安妮。
- Sorry, Mom and Dad, but everybody's been going
- 对不起，爸爸妈妈，但自从美食家先生
to Captain Felde's cafe ever since Gourmet Guy
在他的美食博客上给了船长菲尔德的咖啡馆好评之后，
gave him a rave review on his food blog.
大家就都去那里了。
- His rating scale goes from a "meh" to four "oh, my's."
他的评分标准从“一般般”到四个“哦，我的天”。
- And he just gave Captain Felde's 3 1/2 "oh, my's"
而他刚刚给了Felde船长的咖啡馆3.5个“哦，我的天”。
- How did they get 3 1/2 "oh, my's?"
他们是怎么得到3.5个“哦，我的天”的？
Their new signature dish: the burgerito.
他们的新招牌菜：汉堡卷。
A burger in a burrito on a bun.
一个夹在卷饼里的汉堡。
- Wow, how did they come up with that?
哇，他们是怎么想出来的？
- They did customer research. - Well, how do you know?
他们进行了顾客调研。
- 'Cause we were the customers they researched.
因为我们就是他们调研的顾客。
- I mean, no wonder our only customer is an old lady
难怪我们的唯一顾客是个偷糖包的老太太。
stealing sugar packets.
也许咖啡馆只是需要一些新点子。
- Maybe the cafe just needs some new ideas.
也许这家咖啡馆只是需要一些新点子。
- Yeah, you could always check the suggestion box.
是啊，你可以去看看意见箱。
- Hey, good thinking. I forgot about this thing.
嘿，好主意。我忘了还有这个东西。
It must be 12 years old.
这东西肯定有12年历史了。
[exhales sharply] [coughs]
（深呼吸）（咳嗽）
Ah, here's a suggestion.
啊，这里有个建议。
"Maybe there shouldn't be four crying babies in the store.
“也许店里不应该有四个哭闹的婴儿。
They should be home with their mother."
他们应该和妈妈待在家里。”
[scoffs] What kind of customer writes that?
（嗤之以鼻）什么样的顾客会写这种东西？
See, you don't need a break. [babies crying]
看，你不需要休息。（婴儿哭声）
Maternity leave, shmaternity leave.
产假，什么产假。
- Okay, no need to read any more. [chuckles]
- 好了，不用再读下去了。[轻笑]
They are clearly all old.
他们显然都是老人。
- Well, you know, we could help you guys
- 嗯，你知道，我们可以帮你
and do our own customer research.
并且做我们自己的客户调研。
- Yeah, we'll ask some of our friends about our cafe.
- 是的，我们会问一些朋友关于我们咖啡馆的事。
- Wait, but after burgeritos, right?
- 等等，但吃完汉堡卷之后，对吧？
- Oh, yeah. - Totally.
- 哦，对。 - 当然。
- Of course.
- 当然。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- [whistling]
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome to our customer research session
- 欢迎参加我们在汤姆运动店咖啡厅的顾客调研会议
for the cafe at Tom's Get Sporty.
- 为了感谢您的参与，
To thank you for your participation,
- 每位参与者将获得一份汉堡卷。
you will each get one burgerito.
- 啊，啊，啊，请在完成问卷后领取。
Ah, ah, ah, after you have completed the survey.
[all groaning]
[大家都发出抱怨声]
- We will be asking you a series of questions
- 我们将向您提出一系列问题
and would appreciate your honest opinions.
- 并非常感谢您的诚实意见。
- Let's start with what you like.
- 让我们从您喜欢的事物开始。
I like the smell of those burgeritos.
- 我喜欢那些burgeritos的香味。
- Forget the burgeritos.
- 忘掉那些burgeritos吧。
What do you like about the Get Sporty cafe?
- 您喜欢Get Sporty咖啡馆的哪些方面？
- Uh, the colors are fun.
- 呃，颜色很有趣。
- Those framed sports jerseys are cool.
- 那些装裱起来的运动球衣很酷。
- I feel bigger when I sit at these little tables.
- 我坐在这些小桌子旁时感觉自己变大了。
- Mae?
- 梅？
- I guess if I had to say something,
- 我想如果我必须说点什么，
I don't like these bendy straws.
我不喜欢这些弯曲的吸管。
The noise they make freaks me out.
它们发出的噪音让我感到不安。
- We're naming things we like, Mae.
- 我们在说我们喜欢的东西，梅。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Pass.
跳过。
- What if we had a smoothie we set on fire?
- 如果我们有一种点燃的冰沙呢？
- I'd be into that.
- 我会感兴趣的。
- We're not setting anything on fire.
- 我们不会点燃任何东西。
- No. - [groans]
- 不。 - [呻吟]
- Now let's talk about...
- 现在让我们谈谈...
what you don't like.
你不喜欢的东西。
- Mae? - Pass.
- 梅？ - 跳过。
- Mae? - Seriously.
- 梅？ - 说真的。
I'm not touching this.
我不会碰这个。
- Anyone?
- 有人吗？
all: It's your parents.
所有人: 是你父母。
- Our parents?
- 我们的父母？
- They're always in the cafe. - Because they own it.
- 他们总是在咖啡馆。 - 因为他们拥有它。
- But they're always getting in our biz.
- 但他们总是干涉我们的事。
- And at Captain Felde's cafe,
- 而在费尔德船长的咖啡馆，
we get to hang out with just kids.
我们可以只和孩子们一起玩。
- Sorry, Dawn, but it does feel like your parents
- 抱歉，Dawn，但确实感觉你父母
are always watching us.
一直在监视我们。
- Well, this has been very informative.
- 嗯，这真是非常有启发性。
Thank you for your time.
感谢你的时间。
Enjoy your burgeritos.
享受你的汉堡卷。
- Listen, kids, we may have accidentally overheard
- 听着，孩子们，我们可能不小心听到了
a little bit of what was going on.
一些正在发生的事情。
- And sure, yeah, we may be around sometimes.
当然，是的，我们有时可能会在附近。
- Yeah. - But it's not like we're always
是的。
getting in their "biz."
但我们并不总是闯入他们的'生意'。
[playing accordion] ♪ Mange, mange ♪
♪ 吃吧，吃吧 ♪
♪ How is the pizza? ♪
♪ 披萨怎么样？ ♪
- Ah, ah, ah, not till your homework is finished.
啊，啊，啊，作业做完之前不能吃。
- ♪ Hey, you'll love the straw ♪
♪ 嘿，你会喜欢这吸管的 ♪
♪ And you'll use it every day, hey! ♪
♪ 而且你会每天都用它，嘿！ ♪
Okay, they do have a point. - Yeah.
好吧，他们说得有道理。
- But if the kids don't want us in the cafe,
但如果孩子们不希望我们在咖啡馆里，
how are we gonna fix it?
我们怎么解决这个问题？
- I don't know. We have been having problems
- 我不知道。我们一直都有问题
with it for a while. - Yeah.
已经有一段时间了。- 是的。
With this new competition, I hate to say it, but...
面对这个新的竞争，我虽然不愿意说，但是...
looks like we're going to have to close it down.
看起来我们不得不关闭它了。
- What? - Close it down?
- 什么？- 关闭它？
- Well-- - But we grew up in this cafe.
- 嗯-- - 但我们是在这家咖啡馆长大的。
We have a lot of memories here.
我们在这里有很多回忆。
- Yeah, like when I got hit in the face with that baseball
- 是的，比如我被棒球打中脸
and lost my first tooth.
然后掉了第一颗牙。
- Or when I threw that baseball and knocked out his first tooth.
- 或者当我扔出那个棒球，打掉了他的第一颗牙。
- Exactly. - And I've always had big plans
- 没错。 - 我一直有个大计划
for us to be running it some day.
希望有一天我们能一起经营这家咖啡馆。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
I was thinking of going to college
我原本考虑去上大学
and actually doing something with my life.
并且真正做点什么来改变我的生活。
- Seriously, we're not ready to lose the cafe just yet.
- 说真的，我们还没准备好就这样失去这家咖啡馆。
Can you at least give us the chance to save it first?
你能不能至少给我们一个机会先尝试拯救它？
all: Please!
大家: 拜托！
- Mm-hmm. - Okay, we'll give it a shot.
- 嗯哼。 - 好吧，我们会试试。
- One week, and that's it. - Yep.
- 一周时间，就这样。 - 是的。
- Yes! - Yes, thank you so much.
- 太好了！ - 非常感谢。
We won't let you down. - All right.
我们不会让你失望的。 - 好吧。
I already have my first idea for the cafe.
我已经为咖啡馆想到了第一个主意。
- Good for you. - You're out.
- 不错。 - 你出局了。
- Tough break, Anne. - Wait, what?
- 真遗憾，安妮。 - 等等，什么？
- You're both out. - What?
- 你们俩都出局了。 - 什么？
- Sorry, but the research is never wrong.
- 抱歉，但研究从不出错。
- Ah, man. - Fine.
- 哎，伙计。 - 好吧。
Let's grab one of these for the road.
我们拿一个在路上吃吧。
- No, no, no, no, no.
- 不，不，不，不，不。
burgeritos are for participants only.
汉堡卷只供参赛者食用。
- Fine. - Thank you.
- 好吧。 - 谢谢你。
- Run, Anne! Go, go, go! - Oh, thank you.
- 跑，安妮！快，快，快！ - 哦，谢谢你。
♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Any orders yet? - Nope.
- 有订单吗？ - 没有。
- Any customers? - Nope.
- 有顾客吗？ - 没有。
- Reservations?
- 预订？
- No, but I'm beginning to have a few about opening this place.
- 没有，但我开始对开这家店有些疑虑了。
- Guys, we're not off to a good start.
大家，我们开头可不顺利。
We need customers. - Yeah.
我们需要顾客。- 是啊。
- Oh, oh, here come two now.
- 哦，哦，来了两个。
- Seriously?
- 真的吗？
- Hey, kids.
- 嘿，孩子们。
- all: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 大家：哇，哇，哇。
- Well, just where do you think you're going?
- 你们以为自己要去哪儿呢？
- That doesn't say, "The Parent Cafe."
- 这上面又没写“家长咖啡馆”。
- It says, "The Parent-Free Cafe."
- 写的是“无家长咖啡馆”。
- Guys, we've been watching you for the last two hours,
- 我们已经观察你们俩小时了，
and The Parent-Free Cafe is also customer-free.
而且“无父母咖啡馆”也是无顾客的。
- Clearly, you need us.
- 显然，你们需要我们。
- all: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 等等，等等，等等。
- Let us also remind you of our research.
- 我们也想提醒你们我们的研究。
And I quote... - And he quotes.
而我引用... - 他引用。
- "Your parents are always getting in our biz."
- “你们的父母总是干涉我们的事。”
- End quote. - The quote is over.
- 引用结束。 - 引用结束了。
- Uh, guys, in the future, I'd like to do my own quotes.
- 呃，伙计们，将来我希望自己引用。
- He'd like to do his own quotes.
- 他希望自己引用。
- Okay, well, clearly this isn't working.
- 好吧，显然这行不通。
I mean, even your friends aren't here.
我是说，甚至你的朋友都不在这里。
- Yes, they are. Oh, here they come now.
是的，他们在。哦，他们现在来了。
- And there they go.
他们走了。
- Uh, would you excuse us for one second?
呃，你能让我们单独待一会儿吗？
Uh, what are you guys doing?
呃，你们在干什么？
- Yeah, we made our place parent-free.
是的，我们这里没有家长。
- Yeah, we got buttons.
是的，我们有按钮。
- Why are you still in line for Captain Felde?
你们为什么还在排Captain Felde的队？
- We're not. This is a new line for Pippin's Paninis.
我们不在那儿。这是Pippin's Paninis的新队。
- Gourmet Guy just gave four "oh, my's"
Gourmet Guy刚刚给了四个“哦，我的天”
to their weenie panini. - [chuckles]
对他们的小狗热狗帕尼尼。 - [轻笑]
He said weenie.
他说小狗。
- They put a hot dog inside a panini.
- 他们在帕尼尼里放了一个热狗。
- [chuckles] She said panini.
- [轻笑] 她说帕尼尼。
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
- Okay, all right.
- 好吧，好吧。
At least we know we need more than just no parents.
至少我们知道我们需要的不仅仅是父母不在。
- Yeah. - Wait a minute.
- 是的。 - 等一下。
We need our own burgerito or weenie panini.
我们需要我们自己的汉堡卷或小狗热狗帕尼尼。
- Yeah, we can each come up with a food combo,
- 是的，我们可以每人想出一个食物组合，
then we'll pick the best, and call Gourmet Guy
然后我们会选出最好的，并打电话给美食家盖伊
to come review it. - Yeah.
来让他来评鉴。 - 是啊。
- Wait, you can't just call Gourmet Guy.
- 等等，你不能随便打电话给美食家盖伊。
He doesn't give out his number willy-nilly.
他不会随便把电话号码给别人。
- [chuckles] "Willy-nilly."
- [轻笑] “随便。”
- Fine. We won't call him.
- 好吧。我们不打电话给他。
We'll e-mail him until he agrees.
我们会一直给他发邮件直到他同意。
- In the meantime, we've got two customers at our cafe.
- 与此同时，我们咖啡店有两位顾客。
- Look down at your button, Dicky.
- 看看你的按钮，迪基。
- Oh. [chuckles]
- 哦。[轻笑]
You said button. [laughing]
你说的是按钮。[笑]
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- Why does she keep throwing this thing away?
- 她为什么一直把这个东西扔掉？
This could have some great suggestions in it.
这里面可能有些很棒的建议。
"The owner should lose that awful toupee.
“店主应该丢掉那顶糟糕的假发。
He's not fooling anyone."
他骗不了任何人。”
Huh?
嗯？
- Ah. [chuckles]
- 啊。[轻笑]
- I thought that toupee looked great, Squish.
我觉得那假发挺好的，Squish。
I mean, why would someone--
我是说，为什么有人会——
This is Anne's handwriting.
这是Anne的笔迹。
These are all Anne's.
这些都是Anne的。
[exhales sharply]
（深呼吸）
I do not do little girl push-ups.
我不做小女孩的俯卧撑。
[dog sneezes]
（狗打喷嚏）
Really?
真的吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Thanks for being here, Mae,
谢谢你来这里，Mae，
to help us decide whose fun food combo is the best.
来帮助我们决定谁的趣味食物组合最棒。
- Are you sure you need me to do this?
你确定需要我来评判吗？
- Yeah. We need an impartial judge.
是的，我们需要一个公正的裁判。
- [blows kiss]
（飞吻）
- Uh...pass.
呃...算了。
- Well, I guess we'll have to do it ourselves.
好吧，看来我们得自己来解决了。
I'll start.
我先开始。
I stuffed a pita with a fajita.
我把法吉塔塞进了皮塔饼里。
The fapita.
这就是法皮塔。
Deal with it.
接受吧。
[lid clangs]
[盖子撞击声]
- Ah, impressive, but I see your fapita,
- 啊，不错，但我看到你的fapita，
and I raise you a waffle with falafel in it.
我加一个夹了法拉费的华夫饼。
The waffle-falafel. Deal with that.
华夫法拉费。接受吧。
[lid clangs]
[盖子撞击声]
- Oh, nice try,
- 哦，不错，
but meet...the pizza-dilla.
但看看这个...披萨迪利亚。
Two slices of pizza slapped together to make a quesa-dilla.
两片披萨夹在一起做成一个quesa-dilla。
Boom.
嘣。
- It's pronounced "quesadilla,"
- 那是“quesadilla”，
so it would be the pizzadilla.
所以这应该叫披萨迪利亚。
- I'll say it how I want. It's my i-dilla.
我想怎么说就怎么说。这是我的创意小吃。
[lid crashes] - Ow!
哎哟！
- Okay, no more lid dropping.
好了，不再扔盖子了。
Nicky, what have you got?
尼基，你带来了什么？
- Drum roll, please.
请来个鼓声伴奏。
- Ooh, what is that?
哦，那是什么？
A drumstick inside a dinner roll?
一个鼓槌放在晚餐卷里？
- No, I'm asking for a drum roll.
不，我是让你来个鼓声伴奏。
- Me too. It sounds delicious.
我也是。听起来很美味。
- Ha. The kabob gobbler.
哈，烤肉串大王。
Turkey and all the fixings.
火鸡和所有配菜。
It's Thanksgiving on a stick. Boom.
这是棍子上的感恩节盛宴。砰。
I'd drop this, but I respect my cookware too much.
我想放下这个，但我太尊重我的厨具了。
- All right, let's vote.
- 好吧，我们来投票。
- Vote? [scoffs]
- 投票？[嗤之以鼻]
Please. As the closest thing
拜托。作为这里最接近厨师的人，我知道什么最好,
to a chef here, I know what's best,
那就是烤肉串大王。
and it's the kabob gobbler.
- 呃，显然是法吉塔饼。
- Uh, it's clearly the fapita.
- 呃，华夫饼-法拉费。
- Uh, waffle-falafel.
- 嗯，华夫饼-法拉费。
- Pizza-dilla. - "Dilla."
- 披萨-迪拉。 - "迪拉。"
- Best meal of the year on a stick.
- 今年最棒的一餐，在棍子上。
[all yelling at once]
[大家同时大喊]
- Guys, guys, Gourmet Guy just e-mailed us back.
- 伙计们，伙计们，美食家刚刚给我们回邮件了。
- [gasps] - He's coming tomorrow.
- [倒抽一口气] - 他明天来。
So if we really want to save the cafe,
所以如果我们真的想拯救咖啡馆，
we have to get a good review.
我们必须得到一个好评。
So let's hit him with our best:
所以让我们用我们最好的：
the kabob gobbler.
烤肉吞噬者。
- Nicky, none of us want Mom and Dad to shut down the cafe,
尼基，我们都不希望爸妈关闭咖啡馆，
but we all have to agree.
但我们必须达成一致。
- But since we can't, what are we gonna do?
既然我们无法达成一致，那我们该怎么办？
- I give you the kabob gobbler Waffle-Falafel
我给你带来了烤肉吞噬者华夫饼-法拉费
Fapita Pizza-dilla.
法皮塔披萨-迪拉。
- "Dilla." - Let it go.
“迪拉。” - 算了吧。
- Nicky, as the closest thing we have to a chef,
尼基，作为我们中最接近厨师的人，
what do you think? - [scoffs]
你怎么看？ - [嗤之以鼻]
What do I think?
我怎么看？
I think it lacks focus.
我认为它缺乏焦点。
I think it's a mish mosh of 11 different foods on a stick.
我认为这是11种不同食物串在一起的大杂烩。
I think it's a culinary abomination.
我认为这是烹饪上的亵渎。
- That's a good name.
那是个好名字。
And here's a better one.
这里有个更好的名字。
The Food Bat. [whooshes]
食物蝙蝠。
- You know what? That is a home run.
你知道吗？那真是绝妙的主意。
Hey, check it out. - [gasps]
嘿，看看这个。
- That's gotta be Gourmet Guy.
那一定是美食家先生。
- Okay, guys, it's show time.
好了，伙计们，表演时间到了。
- Table for one, sir?
一位的桌子，先生？
- That'd be lovely.
- Might I recommend our signature dish...
the Food Bat.
- Oh, my.
- [gasps] That's one "oh, my,"
and he hasn't even tasted it.
- Oh, my. - That's two.
- Yes! - That's two.
- [chuckles] Oh, my!
- Three!
- Oh...
哦...
my. - Yes! That's four "oh, my's."
天哪。 - 是的！这是第四个“哦，天哪”。
- Oh, he's so gonna give us a rave review.
哦，他肯定会给我们一个热烈的评价。
- Whoa! - Mmm.
哇！ - 嗯。
all: "Meh"?
大家都说：“一般”？
- How could he give us a "meh"?
他怎么能给我们一个“一般”的评价？
- Maybe we should have set it on fire.
也许我们应该把它点着。
- Dicky, that "meh" could cost us the cafe.
迪基，那个“一般”可能会让我们失去咖啡馆。
- You know, I don't get it.
你知道，我不明白。
We all heard Gourmet Guy say, "Oh, my. Oh, my. Oh, my,
我们都听到美食家说，“哦，天哪。哦，天哪。哦，天哪，
Oh...my."
哦...我的。
Unless... that wasn't Gourmet Guy.
除非...那不是美食家说的。
- But he's the only person we served.
- 但我们只服务了他一个人。
Who else could it have been?
还能是谁说的呢？
- Meh.
- 呃。
What? It...needs salt.
什么？这...需要加点盐。
I think there's some...
我觉得这里有些...
not in here.
不在这里。
- Um, Nicky, did you just say, "meh"?
- 嗯，尼基，你刚才是不是说了“呃”？
- Uh, no, I said, uh, I said, "Mae."
- 呃，没有，我说的是，呃，我说的是“梅”。
- Pretty sure it was "meh."
- 我很确定那是“meh”。
- Well, I'm telling you it was "Mae."
- 我告诉你，那是“Mae”。
- Why would you say "Mae"? She's not even here.
- 你为什么会说是“Mae”？她甚至不在这里。
- You're right. I-I said, "guacmaemole."
- 你说得对。我...我说的是“guacmaemole”。
- Nobody says that.
- 没人这么说。
- Oh, yes, then it must have been, uh, "guacamolmae."
- 哦，是的，那一定是“guacamolmae”。
- No one says that either.
- 也没人这么说。
- Oh, uh, then I meant to say, uh, "guacmaemolmae."
- 哦，那我本来想说“guacmaemolmae”。
Everybody says that.
大家都这么说。
- Is there something you want to tell us, Nicky?
- 你有什么想告诉我们的吗，Nicky？
- I mean, noth--nothing really comes to mind.
我是说，没什么——真的没什么想到的。
Fresh "guacmaemolmae"?
新鲜的“guacmaemolmae”？
- Admit it, you're Gourmet Guy.
承认吧，你就是美食家先生。
- What? No.
什么？不是。
- Admit it!
承认吧！
- Uh, no. - Admit it!
不是。
- Okay, fine. I'm Gourmet Guy.
好吧，好吧。我是美食家先生。
You happy?
你满意了？
- Yeah.
是的。
- What--hey, hey!
什么——嘿，嘿！
Ah!
啊！
This is exactly why Gourmet Guy likes to remain anonymous.
这就是美食家先生喜欢保持匿名的原因。
♪
- What were you thinking, Nicky?
尼基，你当时在想什么？
This could ruin everything we've worked for.
这可能会毁了我们所有努力的一切。
How could you give us a bad review?
你怎么能给我们差评？
- Because...as Gourmet Guy, I have a responsibility
因为...作为美食家先生，我有责任
to give my readers the truth.
向我的读者提供真相。
- Yeah, and as our brother,
是的，作为我们的兄弟，
you also have a responsibility to us.
你也有责任对我们负责。
- I bet he's just mad 'cause we wouldn't
我打赌他只是因为我们不
feature his kabob gobbler.
展示他的烤肉吞食者而生气。
- That's not why I posted it.
我发帖的原因不是这个。
No matter how mad I was as Nicky,
无论我作为尼基有多生气，
as Gourmet Guy, I gave my completely honest opinion.
作为美食家，我给出了完全诚实的意见。
- I'm calling a quaddle.
我要叫停这场争论。
Minus Gourmet Guy.
去掉美食家这个身份。
- Is Nicky still invited?
尼基还受邀吗？
- No! Nicky sits there
不！尼基坐在那里
and thinks about what Gourmet Guy did.
思考美食家所做的事情。
- All right, what do we do?
好吧，我们该怎么办？
- I say we kick him out of the quads.
我说我们应该把他赶出四人组。
From now on, we'll just be the Three Quads.
从现在开始，我们就只是三人组了。
- We can't be the Three Quads, Dicky. Quads means four.
我们不能叫三人组，Dicky。四人组意味着四个人。
- Yeah, just like dilla is pronounced "deya."
对，就像dilla发音为'deya'一样。
- All right, I've got it.
好吧，我想到了。
We'll have Gourmet Guy review us again,
我们会让美食家再评价我们一次，
but this time we'll just serve him Nicky's kabob gobbler.
但这次我们只给他上Nicky的烤肉吞食者。
- Perfect. He's sure to give himself four "oh, my's."
完美。他肯定会给自己四个'哦，我的天'。
- Okay, here's how this is gonna go down.
好的，事情会这样进行。
- Guys, I heard the whole thing.
伙计们，我全听到了。
You're three feet away.
你们就隔了三英尺。
- So, you'll do it, right?
所以，你会做的，对吧？
- Absolutely.
当然。
Nicky looks forward to cooking the kabob gobbler,
尼基期待着烹饪烤肉卷，
and Gourmet Guy looks forward to reviewing it.
而美食家盖伊期待着点评它。
- I'm not sure which one of you I'm talking to,
我不确定我在跟谁说话，
but whoever it is, tell the other one he's weird.
但不管是谁，告诉另一个人他很奇怪。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Hey, Tom, do you have the receipt
嘿，汤姆，你拿到那批长筒袜的收据了吗？
for that tube sock order?
那批袜子订单的发票呢？
- No, but I do have this.
没有，但我有这个。
- Ugh. Did you have to part it, Tom?
哎呀，汤姆，你非得拿出来吗？
- Have to? No.
非得？不。
This is your punishment.
这是对你的惩罚。
- Come on, honey.
拜托，亲爱的。
I wrote those thing, like, right after the kids were born.
我写那些东西，大概是在孩子们刚出生后不久。
I was on no sleep and clearly not thinking straight.
我当时根本没睡觉，显然思维不清。
So please just--just hand over the box.
所以请你就——就把盒子给我吧。
- No, no, no, no, no. - What?
不，不，不，不，不。 什么？
- I want to read the rest of them.
- 我想读完剩下的那些。
I'm sure there's a few in here about my mother.
我确信这里面有几封是关于我母亲的。
- Honey, you are wrong.
- 亲爱的，你错了。
There's more than a few.
不止几封。
- Have you decided on what you'll be having yet, sir?
- 先生，您决定好要点什么了吗？
- Let's see, let's see, let's see.
- 让我看看，让我看看，让我看看。
Do you have any bisque?
你们有海鲜浓汤吗？
- We do not.
- 我们没有。
- Might I suggest the kabob gobbler.
- 我可以推荐烤串大餐吗？
The only thing on the menu.
菜单上唯一的东西。
- Okay, so that's one kabob gobbler.
好的，那么来一份烤肉吞噬者。
- Would you like that set on fire?
您想要点上火吗？
- How does the chef recommend it?
厨师建议怎么吃？
- Not set on fire.
不要点上火。
- One kabob gobbler "not set on fire."
一份烤肉吞噬者，不点火。
- Oh, my. - One!
哦，我的天。一份！
- Oh, my. - Yes! Two!
哦，我的天。是的！两份！
- Oh, my.
哦，我的天。
Oh.
哦。
- all: "Meh?"
大家都：“嗯？”
- Yeah, did you guys call me?
- 是的，你们叫我了吗？
- We weren't talking to you, Mae.
- 我们没在跟你说话，Mae。
How could you give us another "meh?"
你怎么能再给我们一个“meh”？
- I don't get it, Nicky.
- 我不明白，Nicky。
We heard you say "oh, my" four times.
我们听到你说“哦，我的”四次了。
- I said it, but I just couldn't write it.
- 我说了，但我就是写不出来。
- Why not?
- 为什么不行？
The kabob gobbler was your creation.
烤肉吞噬者是你的创意。
- I'm sorry.
- 对不起。
The critic in me has to be honest with the chef in me.
作为评论家的我必须对作为厨师的我说实话。
And the chef in me stinks.
而且我作为厨师做得很差。
- What are you talking about?
你在说什么呢？
We all tasted it, and it was delicious.
我们都尝过了，而且很美味。
- I can't come back from a review like this.
这样的评论让我无法挽回。
- But Gourmet Guy said, "The chef shows promise."
但美食家说：'这位厨师展现出潜力。'
- Well, what does he know? - He's you.
他懂什么？- 他就是你。
- What do I know? - Then don't post it.
我知道什么？- 那就别发了。
- I have to. I have a deadline.
我必须发，我有截稿期限。
- Well, call the editor and tell him
那你打电话给编辑告诉他你赶不上了。
you're not going to make it. - I am also the editor.
我也是编辑。
- Look, you can't post that review.
- 听着，你不能发表那篇评论。
It'll ruin the cafe,
那会毁了这家咖啡馆，
and Mom and Dad will definitely close it down.
爸妈肯定会因此关掉它。
- Hey! - Let go!
- 嘿！ - 放开！
- You let go!
- 你放开！
- [grunts] It's three against one.
- [咕哝] 三对一。
You'll never win. - Wrong.
你赢不了的。 - 错了。
It's three against five.
是三对五。
I'm Gourmet Guy, Chef Nicky, Editor Nicky, and regular Nicky.
我是美食家盖伊，厨师尼基，编辑尼基，还有普通尼基。
- That's four.
- 那是四个。
- Oh. And also Kicky.
哦，还有Kicky。
all: Who? Ow!
谁？哎哟！
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
如果我是你，我不会那么做。
- Step away from the laptop.
离开那台笔记本电脑。
- All of you.
你们所有人。
- Oh, yeah? Who's gonna make me?
哦，是吗？谁会让我这么做？
- Is that a food fight?
那是一场食物大战吗？
This place is picking up.
这个地方越来越热闹了。
- It's not fire, but I'm in.
虽然不是火，但我加入了。
- Food fight!
食物大战！
- [blowing whistle]
- [吹哨]
Everybody, stop! What's wrong with you?
大家，停下！你们怎么了？
This isn't a fair food fight.
这不是公平的食物大战。
Now it's fair. Kabobs away.
现在公平了。烤肉串出击。
[all yelling and laughing]
[所有人叫喊和笑]
- Kids! Kids! - Ah! Ah!
- 孩子们！孩子们！ - 啊！啊！
- Oh, gosh!
- 哦，天哪！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- Hey, hey, stop! Stop!
- 嘿，嘿，停下！停下！
Ahh! - Ow.
啊！ - 哎哟。
- Ow! It totally hurts.
哎哟！真的很疼。
- I thought you wanted to save the cafe,
我以为你想拯救咖啡馆，
not destroy it!
不是要毁了它！
- Sorry, but we found out Nicky's the Gourmet Guy.
对不起，但我们发现尼基就是那位美食评论家。
[all gasping]
（众人惊呼）
- And he was gonna post a bad review about our cafe.
而且他打算对我们咖啡馆发表负面评论。
[all gasping] - Nicky, how could you give us
（众人惊呼）尼基，你怎么能给我们
a bad review? - [gasps]
一个差评？（吸气声）
Oh, we're done with that?
哦，这事已经解决了？
- I'm sorry. I just can't lie to my readers.
我很抱歉。我只是不能对我的读者撒谎。
- We're sorry about all this.
- 我们对这一切感到抱歉。
We just really don't want the cafe to close down.
我们真的不希望咖啡馆关门。
- Well, we have some news
- 嗯，我们有一些消息
and we think you're gonna like it.
我们觉得你会喜欢的。
- We decided to keep it open.
- 我们决定让它继续营业。
- Yes! - You did?
- 太好了！ - 真的吗？
- We saw how much hard work you guys put into saving it,
- 我们看到你们为了挽救它付出了多少努力，
and we realized how much you care about it.
我们意识到你们对它有多么关心。
- Plus, our accountant told us it would be a financial disaster
- 而且，我们的会计告诉我们关闭它会是一场财务灾难
to close it, so...[chuckles] - Yeah.
所以...[轻笑] - 是的。
- [chuckles] Is Nicky your accountant, too?
- [轻笑] Nicky也是你的会计吗？
- No. He is.
- 不是。他是。
- Oh, hi.
- 哦，嗨。
- Okay, let's get this cafe cleaned up
- 好吧，让我们把这个咖啡馆打扫干净，
and back open for business. [all agreeing]
重新开张营业。[大家都同意]
- Uh, is that smoke?
- 呃，那是烟吗？
- Well, that's weird.
- 嗯，这很奇怪。
I preheated the oven, but I didn't put anything in it.
我预热了烤箱，但我没放任何东西进去。
[all panicking]
[大家都惊慌失措]
- Hey, at least something got set on fire.
- 嘿，至少有什么东西被点燃了。
- Run, people!
快跑，大家！
Forget the dinner rolls, Grandma!
别管那些餐卷了，奶奶！
- Ah!
啊！
- Yes! - [screaming]
是的！
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Well, the fire definitely started in the oven.
嗯，火肯定是从烤箱里开始的。
Found this in there.
在那里找到了这个。
- "Suggestion box."
“建议箱。”
- Oops. [chuckles]
哎呀。[轻笑]
Guess that wasn't the best hiding place.
看来那不是最好的藏匿地点。
- Good news. We were also able to save this.
好消息，我们也成功救出了这个。
- Ugh.
呃。
- Thank you, Fireman Handsome-- I mean, Hanson.
谢谢你，帅气的消防员——我是说，汉森。
That's what she calls you.
她就是这么称呼你的。
- Just one time.
就那一次。
- So, how much will it cost to rebuild the cafe?
那么，重建咖啡馆要花多少钱？
- Well...
嗯...
- all: Oh, my.
哦，天哪。
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ [口哨声] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ 耶耶，耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪